Herb Staehr Collection ARC.0029
Library and Archives
Herb Staehr Collection
circa 1950-2007
ARC.0029
Library and Archives
135.75 Linear feet (4 records cartons, 1 Hollinger box, 1 flat box, 114 audiovisual boxes, 7 binders, 1 shared flat file drawer)
The Herb Staehr Collection spans the years circa 1950 to 2007, with the bulk of the material dating between 1968 and 2007. It comprises 138 linear feet of material mainly related to Alvin Lee, Ten Years After, and Eric Clapton, but also to a variety of artists active during the mid-1960s to mid-2000s. Staehr, author of Alvin Lee & Ten Years After: Visual History, was the preeminent collector of Alvin Lee and Ten Years After memorabilia. The bulk of the collection consists of bootleg concert recordings, with some papers, scrapbooks, and photographic material. The collection is divided into seven series: papers, scrapbooks, photographs, slides, negatives, concert recordings, and contact sheets. The collection will be valuable to researchers interested in the history of Ten Years After, English blues-rock, and Woodstock, as well to those looking for images of Eric Clapton or Alvin Lee, and viewing or listening to performances that have not been commercially released.
Biographical Note
1949 Herb Staehr born in Massachusetts.
1969 Attends the Woodstock Festival, where he first hears Ten Years After.
2001 Publishes Alvin Lee and Ten Years After: A Visual History.
2008 Dies of cancer.
Herb Staehr was a collector of photographs and memorabilia related to the English blues-rock band Ten Years After, who performed at Woodstock in 1969. He was the author of Alvin Lee and Ten Years After: A Visual History, regarded as the definitive work on the band.
Sources
"Tribute to Herb Staehr -- Historian of the Band Ten Years After." Ten Years After. Accessed May 13, 2011. http://www.ten-years-after.com/herb/tribute.htm.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights statement on the Researcher Registration form before using this collection. The condition of some of these materials has not yet been determined for playback purposes. Some of the audiovisual materials in the collection are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
Custodial History note
The Herb Staehr Collection was received by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, Inc. as a gift from Thomas W. and Claudia Staehr on December 8, 2008.
Separated Materials
Commercially released CDs, videocassettes, and audiocassettes have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Herb Staehr Collection" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles. If you are unable to find what you are looking for, consult the Library and Archives staff to ensure these materials are available.
Berry, Chuck; Clapton, Eric; Collins, Judy, 1939-; Cream (Musical group); Gladys Knight and the Pips; Hendrix, Jimi; Joplin, Janis; King, B.B.; Led Zeppelin (Musical group); Lee, Alvin; Muddy Waters, 1915-1983; Page, Jimmy; Rolling Stones; Santana (Musical group); Staehr, Herb; Ten Years After (Musical group); Vaughan, Stevie Ray.; Winter, Johnny; Yardbirds (Musical group); Audiocassettes; Blues-rock music; Collectibles; Compact discs; DVD-Video discs; Ephemera; Negatives (photographic); Photographs; Printed ephemera; Scrapbooks; Slides (Photography); Videocassettes
- Series I: Papers, circa 1970s-2007, undated
  Scope and Contents
  Series I: Papers, which spans circa 1970s to 2007 and includes some undated material, is arranged alphabetically by subject. It mainly consists of Staehr’s correspondence and drafts of his book, Alvin Lee and Ten Years After: A Visual History. Clippings come primarily from, but are not limited to, the Dutch music magazine Muziek Express and contain photographs and some music reviews. The video and audio inventories listed at the end of the series likely correspond to the audiovisuals in the collection.
  - Biography, Ten Years After, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Book Web site, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bootleg discographies, Blind Faith and Cream, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings
    - undated (Box 1, Folder 4, Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Eric Clapton
      - 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1994-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence
    - BookMasters (distributor), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Regarding proof sheets and photograph orders, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Regarding Staehr's book
      - 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
      - 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
    - Staehr to Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Foundation, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Larry Yelen, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 17-20)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Draft, Alvin Lee and Ten Years After: A Visual History, circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Draft, cover and text copy, Alvin Lee and Ten Years After: A Visual History, circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Inventory, Ten Years After videos, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Page mock-ups, Alvin Lee and Ten Years After, circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Research files, miscellaneous, 1998-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ten Years After Now tour, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Video and audio inventories
    - Audio and CD, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Video, DVD, and laserdisc, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Video list markup, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Series II: Scrapbooks, circa 1950-2006
  Series II: Scrapbooks spans the years circa 1950 to 2006 and contains the contents of scrapbooks collected by Herb Staehr. All of these materials, now housed in acid-free folders, were originally stored in 3-inch binders. Original order was maintained. The scrapbook materials consist of photographs, clippings, concert tickets, and other documents. The scrapbooks are arranged first by subject matter and then in rough chronological order; many of the scrapbooks represent a broad range of years. Most of the scrapbooks are general collections of ephemera and memorabilia related to Alvin Lee and Ten Years After; there are also a few items related to Eric Clapton, the Yardbirds, and Cream. Of particular interest is one childhood photo of Alvin Lee, taken circa 1950.
  - Alvin Lee and the Alvin Lee Band, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Alvin Lee and Ten Years After
    - circa 1950-1970s (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
    - "1970 Part Two" and other photographs, circa 1970-1980s (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - circa 1970s-1980s (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 9-11)
  - Ten Years After Now tour, 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
  - Ten Years After with Joe Gooch, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ten Years After
    - Bootleg recordings and compilation albums, 1970-2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Concert history
      - circa 1970s-1980s (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
      - 1983-2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - International magazine clippings, circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
    - Record releases, circa 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Song lyrics, 1967-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Eric Clapton, 1990-2006 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Eric Clapton and Cream, 1969-2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Eric Clapton, including audio/video list and photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Yardbirds and Eric Clapton, 1967-1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Alvin Lee and Ten Years After, Eric Clapton, and others, 1973, undated (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Ten Years After, including untitled document by Jim McCullaugh, 1969-1990s, undated (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Series III: Photographs, circa 1960s-2000
  Series III: Photographs spans the years circa 1960s-2000 and consists primarily of images of Alvin Lee and Ten Years After, but also includes a large selection of images of Eric Clapton--with Blind Faith, Cream, solo, and one photo with Muddy Waters and Johnny Winter. In some cases, photographers are attributed. All of these materials were originally collected and stored in 3-inch binders. Original order was maintained where possible.
  - Lee, Alvin, Jayhawks, Ten Years After, circa 1960s-1990s (Drawer-folder FF1.9-8, Object 1, Box 6, Object 1-61, Box 5, Folder 1-5, Box 4, Folder 7-17, Binder 1-3)
  - Blind Faith, Eric Clapton, and Cream, circa 1960s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 6-8, Binder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-1970s (Binder 4)
    General note
    Artists featured in this file include Duane Allman, The Beatles, Jeff Beck, Chuck Berry, Tommy Bolin, Doobie Brothers, Faces, Buddy Guy, Jefferson Airplane, Led Zeppelin, Lynyrd Skynyrd, The Rolling Stones, Linda Ronstadt, Bruce Springsteen, Rod Stewart, Jimmie Vaughan, Stevie Ray Vaughan, The Who, and The Yardbirds.
- Series IV: Slides, circa 1968-2000 (Binder 5-6)
  Series IV: Slides spans the years circa 1968 to 2000 and consists of archival binders of mylar pages holding slides. The images represented here are mostly of Alvin Lee and Ten Years After performances, but also include concert images of Chuck Berry, Blind Faith, Eric Clapton, Judy Collins, Cream, Bob Dylan, John Fogerty, Janis Joplin, B.B. King, Gladys Knight and the Pips, Moody Blues, Rolling Stones, Linda Ronstadt, Santana, and Tina Turner, as well as images of concert posters.
- Series V: Negatives, circa 1968-2000 (Binder 7)
  Series V: Negatives spans the years circa 1968 to 2000 and consists primarily of live concert images of Alvin Lee and Ten Years After, but also includes images of performances by Blind Faith, Eric Clapton, Cream, Jimi Hendrix, Led Zeppelin, Muddy Waters, Stevie Ray Vaughan, and Johnny Winter, as well as images of concert posters.
- Series VI: Concert, Studio, and Television Recordings [RESTRICTED], circa 1960s-2000s
  Series VI: Concert, Studio, and Television Recordings spans the years circa 1960s to 2000s and comprises nearly a third of the entire Herb Staehr Collection. The Series consists of seven subseries, each of which corresponds to a particular audio or video format: CD, audiocassette, DVD, Beta, VHS, film, and minidisc. Most of the recordings are of Alvin Lee, Ten Years After, Eric Clapton, and Cream. Subseries 1, 2, 6, and 7 include item-level inventories. For researchers interested in the materials in Subseries 3-5, please contact Library and Archives staff for additional information.
  Access Restrictions
  The condition of some of these materials has not yet been determined for playback purposes. Some of the audiovisual materials in the collection are on defunct media formats and, therefore, are RESTRICTED. Access copies of these materials may have to be created prior to use. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
  - Subseries 1: Compact Discs, circa 1960s-2000s
    Subseries 1: Compact Discs, circa 1960s-2000s are organized alphabetically by performer. In instances where there is more than one CD for a performer or group, the CDs have been arranged chronologically.
    - Adams, Bryan: Johanneshow Isstadion, Stockholm, Sweden with Alvin Lee, 1987 November 20 (Box 6, Object 62)
    - Allman Brothers Band: Fillmore West, 1971 January 29 (Box 6, Object 63-64)
      Master from Wolfgang's Vault Radio.
    - Animals
      - Poughkeepsie, New York, 1983 (Box 6, Object 65-66)
      - Royal Oak Music Theater, Illinois, 1983 November 29 (Box 6, Object 67-68)
        General Note
    - Beck, Jeff and Ten Years After, 1969 July 12 (Box 6, Object 69)
    - Bloomfield, Mike: Fillmore West, San Francisco, California, 1969 February 1-1969 February 2 (Box 6, Object 70-71)
    - Bruce, Jack
      - Bonn, Germany, 1977 October 1 (Box 6, Object 72)
      - Jack Bruce Band, London, England, 1998 July 18 (Box 6, Object 73-74)
    - Byrds at Avalon Ballroom, San Francisco, California, 1968 November 2 (Box 6, Object 75)
    - Canned Heat
      - Newark State College, 1970 December 5 (Box 6, Object 76)
        Vault radio master.
      - Parr Meadows, Long Island, New York, 1979 September 7 (Box 6, Object 77)
    - Clapton, Eric
      - Houston, Texas, 1976 November 13 (Box 6, Object 78-79)
      - Dallas Convention Center, Dallas, Texas, 1976 November 15 (Box 6, Object 80)
        Track list: "Hello Friend," "Sign Language," "Knockin' on Heaven's Door," "Blues Power," "Crowd," "Layla." Master from Wolfgang's Vault Radio.
      - Santa Monica Civic Auditorium, Santa Monica, California, 1978 February 12 (Box 6, Object 81-82)
      - The Lost Israel Tapes, Jerusalem, Israel, 1979 October 29 (Box 6, Object 83)
      - Capital Center, Washington, D.C., 1983 February 28 (Box 6, Object 84-85)
      - Landover, Maryland, 1983 February 28 (Box 6, Object 86-87)
      - Centrum, Worcester, Massachusetts, 1994 October 14 (Box 6, Object 88-89)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 2001 February 4, 2001 February 9-2001 February 10 (Box 6, Object 90-95)
      - Toulouse, France, 2001 February 26 (Box 6, Object 96-97)
      - NPR interviews, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Object 98)
      - Slowhand at 60, BBC Radio 2, 2005 (Box 6, Object 99-100)
      - Le Cannet, France, 2006 May 5 (Box 6, Object 101-102)
        First show of tour.
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 2006 May 25 (Box 6, Object 103-104)
      - Stuttgart, Germany, 2006 June 3 (Box 6, Object 105-106)
      - Lucca, Italy, 2006 July 7 (Box 6, Object 107-108)
      - Locarno, Switzerland, 2006 July 11 (Box 6, Object 109-110)
      - Augustenborg, Denmark, 2006 July 26 (Box 6, Object 111-112)
      - Columbus, Ohio, with Jimmie Vaughan, 2006 August 13 (Box 6, Object 113)
      - Chicago, Illinois, 2006 September 20 (Box 6, Object 114-115)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 2006 September 29 (Box 6, Object 116-117)
      - Washington, D.C., 2006 October 10 (Box 6, Object 118-119)
      - Charlottesville, Virginia, 2006 October 12 (Box 6, Object 120)
      - Sapporo, 2006 November 26 (Box 6, Object 121-122)
      - Nagoya, Japan, 2006 November 17-2006 November 18 (Box 6, Object 123-126)
      - Tokyo, Japan, 2006 November 20-2006 December 9 (Box 6, Object 127-136)
      - Hong Kong, China, 2007 January 17 (Box 6, Object 137-138)
      - Shanghai, China, 2007 January 20 (Box 6, Object 139-140)
      - Sydney, Australia, 2007 January 29 (Box 6, Object 141-142)
      - San Jose, California, 2007 March 3 (Box 6, Object 143-144)
      - Auburn Hills, Detroit, 2007 April 5 (Box 6, Object 145-146)
      - Columbus, Ohio, 2007 April 6 (Box 6, Object 147-148)
    - Cocker, Joe: "Freeway Series," Hollywood Bowl and Long Beach, California, 1972 (Box 6, Object 149)
    - Cream
      - Disraeli Gears sessions, Spot Studio, London, England, 1967 March 15 (Box 6, Object 150)
      - Whisky-A-Go-Go, Los Angeles, California, 1967 September 4 (Box 6, Object 151-152)
      - Winterland, San Francisco, California, 1968 March 10 (Box 6, Object 153-154)
      - Oakland Coliseum, Oakland, California and Los Angeles Forum, Los Angeles, California, 1968 October 4, 1968 October 19 (Box 6, Object 155-156)
      - Omnibus Show, Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1968 (Box 6, Object 157)
        From master.
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 2005 May 5 (Box 6, Object 158-160, 167)
        Object 160 contains video clips.
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 2005 October 24-2005 October 26 (Box 6, Object 161-167)
    - Creedence Clearwater Revival
      - Fillmore West, San Francisco, California, 1969 March 14, 1971 July 4 (Box 6, Object 168-170)
      - Boston Garden, Boston, Massachusetts, 1971 July 16 (Box 6, Object 171)
    - Crosby, Stills, Nash and Young: Fillmore East, New York, New York, 1970 June 6 (Box 6, Object 172)
    - Crossroads Guitar Festival
      - Toyota Park, Bridgeview, Illinois, Set 1 - Set 4, 2007 July 28 (Box 6, Object 173-181)
      - Master, undated (Box 6, Object 182)
    - Delaney & Bonnie and Friends including Eric Clapton: Fillmore West, San Francisco, California, 1970 February 22 (Box 6, Object 183)
    - Elvin Bishop Group at Fillmore West, San Francisco, California, 1971 July 1 (Box 6, Object 184)
    - Fleetwood Mac
      - Carousel Ballroom, San Francisco, California, 1968 June 8, 1968 June 23 (Box 6, Object 185-186)
      - Konserthuset, Stockholm, Sweden, 1969 March 23 (Box 6, Object 187)
      - Capitol Theater, Passaic, New Jersey, 1975 June 7 (Box 6, Object 188)
    - Humble Pie: Winterland, San Francisco, California, 1973 May 26 (Box 6, Object 189)
    - Jefferson Airplane: O'Keefe Center, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1967 August 5 (Box 6, Object 190)
    - Jethro Tull: Boston Tea Party, Boston, Massachusetts, 1969 December 9 (Box 6, Object 191)
    - Joplin, Janis: Fillmore East, New York, New York, 1969 February 12 (Box 6, Object 192)
    - King, Freddie: Ultrasonic Studios (WLIR), Hempstead, New York, 1973 (Box 6, Object 193)
    - Led Zeppelin, 1969
      - Fillmore West, San Francisco, California, 1969 April 27 (Box 6, Object 194-195)
      - Dallas, Texas, 1969 August 31 (Box 6, Object 196-197)
    - Lee, Alvin, 1975-2004, 2007
      - Alvin Lee and Company at Orpheum, Boston, Massachusetts, 1975 January 10 (Box 6, Object 198-199)
      - With Ten Years Later, Bolero studio jams, 1977 (Box 6, Object 200)
      - With Micki Taylor, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Object 201)
      - Plazza Blues, Bellinzona, Italy, 2004 (Box 6, Object 202-203)
      - Saguitar, 2007 (Box 6, Object 204)
    - Plant, Robert: Finlandia Hall, Helsinki, Finland, 2002 November 11 (Box 6, Object 205-206)
    - Rolling Stones: Boston Garden, Boston, Massachusetts, 1972 July 19 (Box 6, Object 207)
    - Ronstadt, Linda: Calderone Concert Hall, Hempstead, New York, 1975 January 29 (Box 6, Object 208)
    - Savoy Brown at Record Plant, Sausalito, California, 1975 November 24 (Box 6, Object 209)
    - Ten Years After
      - Various including Jaybids "Not Fade Away," Swedish television, Newport Jazz Festival, 1964, 1968-197 (Box 6, Object 210)
      - BBC: Top Gear, Dave Symonds, and Colour Me Pop, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Object 211)
      - Fillmore West, San Francisco, California, 1968 June 28 (Box 6, Object 212-214)
      - BBC, 1968 August 16 (Box 6, Object 215)
      - Fillmore East, New York, New York; Top Gear, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Object 1)
      - Concerthouse, Stockholm, Sweden; Swedish TV; BBC Radio, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Object 2)
      - Boston, Massachusetts and Swedish TV, 1968 September 20, 1970 February 16 (Box 7, Object 3)
      - BBC: Colour Me Pop, 1969 January (Box 7, Object 4)
      - Eagles Auditorium, Seattle, Washington and Palalido, Milan, Italy, 1969 March 22, 1971 March (Box 7, Object 5)
      - Helsinki, Finland, 1969 December 3 (Box 7, Object 6)
      - Swingin' / Rockin', 1969 (Box 7, Object 7)
      - Isle of Wight Festival, 1970 August 30 (Box 7, Object 8)
      - Boston Tea Party, Boston, Massachusetts, 1970 (Box 7, Object 9)
      - Winterland Arena, San Francisco, California, 1971 April 30 (Box 7, Object 10-11)
      - Maple Leaf Garden, Toronto, Ontario, 1972 September 26 (Box 7, Object 12)
      - Festhalle, Frankfurt, Germany, 1973 January 28 (Box 7, Object 13-14)
      - Boston Music Hall, Boston, Massachusetts, 1974 May 15 (Box 7, Object 15-16)
      - Park West, Chicago, Illinois, 1983 October 21 (Box 7, Object 17-18)
      - Blues Festival, Telegen, Holland, 1988 September (Box 7, Object 19)
      - Giessen, Germany, 1988 (Box 7, Object 20)
      - Mainz, Germany, 1990 February 27 (Box 7, Object 21)
      - Serenadenhof, Nuremberg, Germany, 1999 July 7 (Box 7, Object 22-23)
      - House of Blues, Los Angeles, California, 1999 September 9 (Box 7, Object 24-25)
      - Paul Jones Show; Herzberg; Laisladel; Blues Warehouse, 2003, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Object 26-27)
      - Interviews, 2003, 2006 (Box 7, Object 28)
      - Now, 2004 (Box 7, Object 29)
      - Roadworks, 2005 (Box 7, Object 30-31)
      - Blues Warehouse, Long Island, New York, hosted by Mark Klein, 2006 March 13 (Box 7, Object 32-34)
      - Lovely Days Festival, St. Pölten, Austria, 2007? (Box 7, Object 35)
      - Spectrum, Augsburg, Germany, 2007 January 15 (Box 7, Object 36-37)
      - Sellersville Theater, Sellersville, Pennsylvania, 2007 May 23 (Box 7, Object 38-39)
      - Altlengbach, Austria, 2007 June 1 (Box 7, Object 40)
      - Leo Lyons interview, WNTI radio, 2007 July 5 (Box 7, Object 41)
      - Lovely Days Festival, St. Pölten, Austria, 2007 July 6 (Box 7, Object 42-44)
        Two disc set contains Jethro Tull's performance at the Lonely Days Festival.
      - Audio tracks for 40 year anniversary video, circa 2007 (Box 7, Object 45)
    - Traffic
      - Boston Tea Party, Boston, Massachusetts, 1970 June 7 (Box 7, Object 46)
      - Fillmore East, New York, New York, 1970 November 18 (Box 7, Object 47)
    - The Who
      - Fillmore East, New York, New York, 1968 April 6, 1969 October 22 (Box 7, Object 48-49)
      - Summit, Houston, Texas, 1975 November 20 (Box 7, Object 50-51)
  - Subseries 2: DVD-Video, circa 1960s-2000s
    Subseries 2: DVD-Video, circa 1960s-2000s, are organized alphabetically by performer. In instances where there is more than one DVD for a performer or group, the DVDs have been arranged chronologically. Award ceremonies, documentaries, music festivals, television series and specials, and compilations of footage will be found under "Various" in alphabetical order by program title or event; then chronologically where necessary. Please note, the order in which the DVDs appear in the finding aid is not always the same as the physical order of the materials, as some discs contain multiple artists and/or events.
    - ABBA
      - Top of the Pops; Live in London, 1979 (Box 7, Object 52)
      - Music show, Japan; Story, 1974-1982, undated (Box 7, Object 53)
    - AC/DC
      - Sight and Sound; Rock Goes to College; Glasgow, Scotland; French television interview and live, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Object 54)
      - Let There Be Rock, Paris, France, 1980 (Box 7, Object 55)
      - Live in Japan; MTV Rockumentary, 1981, 1991 (Box 7, Object 56)
    - Adams, Bryan: Live Aid, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; Tokyo Dome, Japan, 1985 July 13, 1989 December 31 (Box 7, Object 57)
    - Aerosmith
      - Texas Jam, Cotton Bowl, Dallas, Texas; California Jam II, 1978 March 18, 1978 July 4 (Box 7, Object 58)
      - Orpheum Theater, Boston, Massachusetts; Monsters if Rock Weekend on MTV, 1984 December 31, 1989 (Box 7, Object 59)
      - Get a Grip MTV Rockumentary; MTV Unplugged, 1990, undated (Box 7, Object 60)
      - Woodstock, Saugerties, New York, 1994 August 14 (Box 7, Object 61)
    - Allman Brothers
      - Fillmore East, New York, New York; Love Valley, North Carolina, 1970 (Box 7, Object 62)
      - Various including Saturday Night in Macon, In Concert, live in Paris, Saturday Night Live, 1973, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Object 63)
      - Don Kirshner's Rock Concert, 1975 (Box 7, Object 142)
      - 1985, undated (Box 7, Object 64)
      - Red Rocks, Denver, Colorado, 1989 July 31 (Box 7, Object 65)
      - Mosque, Richmond, Virginia, 1989 October 11 (Box 7, Object 66-67)
      - Shoreline Amphitheater, Mountainview, California, 1989 (Box 7, Object 68-69)
      - Chastain Park, Atlanta, Georgia, 1990 July 2 (Box 7, Object 70-71)
      - Jones Beach, Long Island, New York; The Tonight Show Sttarring Johnny Carson, 1990 August 1, 1990 August 31 (Box 7, Object 72-73)
      - Lakewood Amphitheater, Atlanta, Georgia, 1990 November 9 (Box 7, Object 74-75)
      - MTV Unplugged [unedited], 1990 (Box 7, Object 67)
      - One to One, VH-1 Special, 1990 (Box 7, Object 69)
      - 1991 February (Box 7, Object 76)
      - Jones Beach, Long Island, New York, 1991 September 4 (Box 7, Object 77)
      - Great Woods, Mansfield, Massachusetts; ABC in Concert, 1991 September 6, 1992 (Box 7, Object 78)